thebusinessdesk.com 2018-12-23

# Cookies and Privacy | TheBusinessDesk.com

**Introduction** Our website uses ‘cookies', which are small data files that are used as unique identifiers. They are sent from the website's servers to your computer or mobile phone and stored on your device, and may then be sent back to our website's servers with updated data as you browse our website. Cookies are used to record information about your preferences as you browse our website, which allows us to improve your experience by tailoring the website accordingly. Cookies can also be used to identify you every time you revisit our website. A ‘session cookie' will expire at the end of your browsing session once you close your web browser; ‘persistent cookies' on the other hand have a set expiry date and will be stored on your computer until either this date is reached, or you delete your cookies using your browser settings.   **How We Use Cookies** The following is a list of cookies used by our website, and what they are used for:  **Cookie Name** | **Cookie Type** | **Description**  
---|---|---  
PHPSESSID saved_region_new current_region splash_banner_700 uername password | Session Cookie | The Business Desk website uses a session cookie to maintain information about each visit to the website and enable core site functionality. This cookie does not contain any personal information, and only lasts for the duration of your visit, being deleted as soon as you close your web browser.  
AWSELB | Load Balancer Cookie | This cookie is essential to help ensure that the website loads efficiently by distributing visits across multiple web servers. This cookie does not contain any personal information, and only lasts for the duration of your visit, being deleted as soon as you close your web browser.  
_utma _utmb _utmc _utmz | Google Analytics | This cookie allows us to count page visits and traffic sources, so we can measure and improve the performance of our site, using a service provided by Google Analytics. For more information about Google's privacy policy, please use this link [www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy)  
  **Third-Party Cookies** Our website uses the following third-party suppliers and partners who may also set cookies on your computer or mobile phone as you browse our website. If you would like to know more about how these third-parties use cookies to collect and store your data, please use the links below:  **Cookie Name** | **Cookie Type** | **Description**  
---|---|---  
_atuvc, loc, uit, dt, di, uid, uvc, psc | AddThis Cookies | These cookies are used to collect information about how our visitors use the AddThis function provided on the website. We use this information to compile reports to help us improve our site. The cookies collect information such as pages viewed and sites added using this service. Please note these cookies only personally identify you if you have already independently signed up with AddThis and have given your consent. Please visit [www.addthis.com/privacy](http://www.addthis.com/privacy) for more information.  
NID, PREF | Google+1 Cookies | The Google+ plugin on our website allows you to promote our website to your contacts using the ‘+1' button. These cookies are installed by Google to detect if you are currently logged in with a Google account. For more information, please see [www.google.co.uk/intl/en-GB/policies](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en-GB/policies).  
guest_id, pid, k | Twitter Cookies | The Twitter plugin on our website allows you to quickly follow our official Twitter account. These cookies are installed by Twitter, and are used to detect if you are currently logged into Twitter when you visit our website, and if you are already following us. For more information, please see <http://twitter.com/privacy>.  
datr | Facebook Cookie | The Facebook plugin on our website allows you to quickly ‘Like' our official Facebook page. This cookie is installed by Facebook, and is used to detect if you are currently logged into Facebook when you visit our website, as well as if you already ‘Like' our Facebook page. Please see [www.facebook.com/about/privacy](http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy) for more information.  
id | DoubleClick Cookie | This cookie is installed by Google to collect anonymous browsing behaviour and serve content, advertisements and other information to you, based on your interests. Please note that no personally identifiable information is recorded. Please visit [www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ads](http://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ads) for more information.  
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE PREF | YouTube Cookies | These cookies are installed by YouTube, and track your preferences when you view embedded video content on our site. Please visit [www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy) for more information.  
  AA002, MUID | Atlas Solutions Cookies | These cookies are installed by a third party, Atlas Solutions, which is part of Microsoft Advertising. They are used to track and deliver targeted advertising to web users based on their browsing behaviour. For more information, please visit <http://atlassolutions.com/privacy-policy>.  
Please note that, where we embed content from third-party sites such as Flickr and YouTube, you may also have cookies from these third-party websites installed on your device. The Business Desk does not control these cookies and you should check the privacy policy of the relevant website for more information. Please also note that, if you use one of the ‘sharing tools' on our website to share content using social networks, these social networks may install a cookie on your device. The Business Desk does not control these cookies and you should check the privacy policy of the relevant website for more information.   ****Blocking Cookies**** The majority of web browsers (Firefox, Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Opera, Safari etc.) will allow you to block cookies from being installed on your device via your browser settings. Depending on your browser, further information can be obtained via the following links: 

  * Firefox - <http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Cookies>
  * Internet Explorer - <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/196955>
  * Google Chrome - [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)
  * Safari - <http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/3.0/en/9277.html>
  * Opera - <http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/>

Mobile phone users may have to refer to their handset manual for details on how to block cookies using their mobile browser. Please be aware that restricting the use of cookies may impact on the functionality of our website.   ****Deleting Cookies**** The majority of web browsers (Firefox, Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Opera, Safari etc.) will allow also allow you to delete selected / all cookies currently installed on your device. Depending on your browser, further information can be obtained via the following links: 

  * Firefox - <http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Cookies>
  * Internet Explorer - <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/196955>
  * Google Chrome - [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)
  * Safari - <http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/3.0/en/9277.html>
  * Opera - <http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/>

Similarly, mobile phone users may have to refer to their handset manual for details on how to delete cookies using their mobile browser. Please note that this will usually only remove any cookies currently installed on your device; you must also change your browser settings (above) if you wish to prevent cookies being installed in future. Please be aware that deleting cookies already stored on your device may impact on the usability of our website.   ****Contact Details and Useful Information**** This website is owned and operated by The Business Desk. If you have any questions about our use of cookies and how we collect and store your data, then please contact [admin@thebusinessdesk.com](mailto:admin@thebusinessdesk.com). For more information on cookies and how they work, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>.    

## Privacy Policy

**W** **elcome to Regional Media Services Ltd t/a TheBusinessDesk.com’s privacy policy.** ** ** **We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data.**

## Introduction

This privacy policy tells you how Regional Media Services Ltd uses your personal data when you visit our website, interact with us, and buy our goods and services. It also tells you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you. It is important that you read this privacy policy, together with any other privacy policies we may provide, so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. If you have any questions, or would like to exercise your privacy rights, please follow the instructions in this privacy policy. See How to contact Regional Media Services Ltd about privacy below. In general, you may visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about you. Our servers collect the domain names, operating system in use (e.g., Macintosh, Windows) and browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox). This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed, etc. Regional Media Services Ltd uses this information to measure the use of our Site and to improve the content of our Site. E-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information such as first and last name, home or other physical address, telephone number, and other similar information are known only when voluntarily provided by a visitor for registration or other participation of visitors in any available online interactive activities. Unless otherwise disclosed during the collection, personally identifiable information that may be collected in connection with visitors to this Site is retained by Regional Media Services Ltd. Regional Media Services Ltd does not sell, transfer or otherwise disclose this personally identifiable information outside this company, except where disclosure is required by law or where consent has been obtained to its disclosure from you. We do not transfer such information outside the European Union. It is our policy that visitors to our Site who are under the age of 18 should not post or provide information on our Site without the consent of their parents or legal guardians. You should supervise the online activities of your children, and consider the use of parental control tools available from online services and software providers that help provide a kid-friendly Internet environment. We may use the personal information you provide for any of the following purposes: (1) to understand the use of our Site and make improvements; (2) to respond to specific request from visitors; (3) to obtain parental consent from visitors under 18 years of age, where necessary; (4) to provide any necessary notices to our visitors or their parent or legal guardians, where necessary; (5) to protect the security or integrity of our Site when necessary; (6) to send you notices and communications regarding the Site and our businesses; (7) in general to promote and market products to you. Communications may take the form of mailings, telephone calls, e-mails and other methods of contact. If you do not want to receive these communications from us using your personally identifiable information, please notify us. At times, we conduct on-line surveys to better understand the needs and profiles of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will let you know how we will use the information at the time we collect the information from you on the Internet. 

## Security and data retention

We employ appropriate security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.   We have procedures in place to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so. We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. For more information on our retention periods please contact us. We will keep information which we hold about you up to date. 

## Accessing and updating

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us. 

## Individual rights

  * You have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data:
  * The right to be informed – that’s an obligation on us to inform you how we use your personal data (and that’s what we’re doing that in this privacy policy);
  * The right of access – that’s a right to make what’s known as a ‘data subject access request’ for copy of the personal data we hold about you;
  * The right to rectification – that’s a right to make us correct personal data about you that may be incomplete or inaccurate;
  * The right to erasure – that’s also known as the ‘right to be forgotten’ where in certain circumstances you can ask us to delete the personal data we have about you (unless there’s an overriding legal reason we need to keep it);
  * The right to restrict processing – that’s a right for you in certain circumstances to ask us to suspend processing personal data;
  * The right to data portability – that’s a right for you to ask us for a copy of your personal data in a common format (for example, a .csv file);
  * The right to object – that’s a right for you to object to us processing your personal data (for example, if you object to us processing your data for direct marketing); and
  * Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling – that’s a right you have for us to be transparent about any profiling we do, or any automated decision making.

These rights are subject to certain rules around when you can exercise them. If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us. We try to respond to all legitimate requests within **one month**. Occasionally, it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated. We may share your personal data with the parties set out below for the purposes set out in this privacy policy. We may also share your personal data if the law otherwise allows it.  

## Sharing your data

We may share personal data with the following categories third parties: 

  * Suppliers and service providers (such as technology service providers, payment processing and fraud prevention providers, manufacturers and post and courier services);
  * auditors and professional advisers like bankers, lawyers, accountants and insurers; and
  * government, regulators and law enforcement.

We share personal data with the following specific third parties: 
  * _Barques Design_ : We share your data with Barques Design in the context that they host and manage our Website and send our direct marketing campaigns to prospective and current customers.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions. 

## Changes to our privacy policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. As it may change, we ask you to revisit this page when you visit our Site to review the current policy. If you do not agree with the policy, you should cease use of the Site immediately. Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification. 

## Third Party Links

This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications (for example, the ability to sign in with Facebook). Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit. 

## Contact

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to the addresses, or by telephone to the numbers, shown on our "Contact Us" page on this site. Should you wish to see a copy of our Data Protection Policy please request this through our "Contact Us" page.
